Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications
1944-2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2374
184 Linear Feet
This collection contains photographs, slides, film and a small number of paper records with materials such as press releases, public hearings, planning records, newspaper articles, and memoranda related to the construction of Metro. These records were produced by Larry Levine while employed by WMATA as a staff photographer. These materials cover the years 1944-2003. Additional materials were added to Series 1 that include publications about the Metro, produced by both WMATA and outside sources, which cover the years 1963 to 2014. These items were not necessarily created by Larry Levine during his time at WMATA.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Photographic material and paper records and Audio/Visual material
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Wasington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 2018 (2018.026).
Scope and Contents
This collection contains photographs, slides, film and a small number of paper records with materials such as press releases, public hearings, planning records, newspaper articles, and memoranda related to the construction of Metro. These records were produced by Larry Levine, Paul Myatt, and Phil Portlock while employed by WMATA as staff photographers. These materials cover the years 1944-2003. Additional materials were added to Series 1 that include publications about the Metro, produced by both WMATA and outside sources, which cover the years 1963 to 2014. These items were not necessarily created by Larry Levine during his time at WMATA.
Biographical / Historical
The Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, WMATA, with central offices in Washington, DC, is the private agency charged with the coordination and operation of mass transit in the National Capital Region. This area includes Montgomery and Prince George's Counties in Maryland, Arlington, the District of Columbia, and Fairfax County in Virginia. The Interim Board of Directors of WMATA first met in mid-October, 1966, chaired by Brig. Gen. Jackson Graham, formerly Engineering Commissioner for the District. WMATA was formally established on February 20, 1967. WMATA formally received its charter in September 1967. WMATA superseded the National Capital Transportation Agency (NCTA); a federal agency established by President Eisenhower in 1960 and inherited the bus and rail plans of the NCTA. For bus operations, WMATA bought out the routes from the private bus companies operating within its purview (with the exception of Montgomery County's "Ride-On" system) and established a single operation, Metrobus, to serve in their place. For the creation of Metrorail, popularly known as "the Metro," routes, designs, and plans were finalized by the late 1960s. Work on the subway component began immediately upon the creation of WMATA. DeLeuw, Cather were retained as chief engineering consultants. The firm of Harry Weese and Associates were named chief architectural consultants. Weese was sent on a worldwide tour of subway systems, in order to draw inspiration and ideas for possible station architecture. The final design, agreed upon by a special committee that included the District of Columbia Board of Fine Arts and several artists and architects, was proposed in 1968. First ground was broken for the subway above the future Judiciary Square station on December 9, 1969. The Metro ran its first day of revenue service, on the abbreviated Red Line beginning at Dupont Circle, in June 1976. Public response was enthusiastic. The system was a highlight of the Bicentennial celebrations one month later, during which it transported thousands of visitors.
Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Regulation Compact; Urban transportation; Transportation -- Washington Metropolitan Area; City planning -- Washington (D.C.); Architecture -- Washington (D.C.); Building construction
- Photographic material and paper records, Series 1
  Arrangement
  Organized into 5 subseries: Negatives, Prints, Contact sheets, Color slides, and Publications
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains negatives, prints, slides, contact prints, paper records, and publications that are composed of memoranda, event programs, publicity, newspaper articles, biographical records, and organizational information.
  - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Labels and Note Cards, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Negatives, 1944-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Negatives, 1947-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, O-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, P-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, R-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, S-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, Staff Portraits, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22B, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, T-Files [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22C, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, T-Files [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22C, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, U-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22C, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, V-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22C, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, W-Files, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 22C, Folder 5)
    - Street Scenes [1 of 5], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78A, Folder 1)
    - Street Scenes [2 of 5], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78A, Folder 2)
    - Street Scenes [3 of 5], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78A, Folder 3)
    - Street Scenes [4 of 5], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78A, Folder 4)
    - Street Scenes [5 of 5], Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78A, Folder 5)
  - Prints, Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Southwest Terminal, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Special Events 1, 1980-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Special Events 2, 1995-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Recreation-Sports, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Staff, 1980-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Staff, 1969-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Exta, 1983-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Staff: Admin, Acct, Audit, 1962-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Staff: General Managers, 1975-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Staff: General Managers, 1991-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Staff: Govr.,Labr., Misv., 1984-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Staff: Officers, 1980-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Construction: Cut and Cover, 1975-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Construction: St. Scenes/ Work Men, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Construction: St. Scenes/ Work Men, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Construction: Sunface, 1974-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Trolley Cars, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Metro Bus: Doc. Shots, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Exhibits, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Fare Card, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Geology Cross-Section, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Ground Breaking DC, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Bus Rodeo, 1977-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bus and Rail Signs, 1975-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bus Supv/ Admin Depot Clerks, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bus Supv/ Admin Depot Clerks, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bus Shelters, 1973-1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bus Training, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Charts, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - City Connections, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Construction: Aerials, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Construction, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Construction: Stations, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Poster Contest, 1975-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Production Stills, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Potomac River, 1975-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Project Building, 1970-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pylon, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Rail Admin, 1983-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Rail Mechanics, 1983-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rail System Maintenance, 1980-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Rail Plant Maintenance, 1985-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Rail Roadeo, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Rail Station Managers, 1976-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Rail Track and Structure, 1984-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Rail Training, 1976-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Repair Shop, 1976-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Seals of Jurisdiction, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Security, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Snow Pictures, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Soil Testing, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Trains Start Up, 1979-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Trains Various S & I Yards, 1983-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Trains: Winder 6A, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Uniforms, 1974-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Vandalism: Bus and Rail, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - VIP, 1975-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Woodward and Lothrop, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Gunn, David L., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Jackson [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Graham, Jackson [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Benjamin, Peter, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Catoe, John B. Jr, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Metro Art Work, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Pfanstiehl, Cody - Bio [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Pfanstiehl, Cody - Bio [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Misc Slide Show [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Misc Slide Show, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Helicopter Flight Patterns [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Helicopter Flight Patterns [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - D. Parking, 1953-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 1)
    - D-2. Multi-story Structures, 1956-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 2)
    - D-3 Rooftop or part of structure parking, 1953-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 3)
    - E-1 Residential, 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
    - E-2 Commercial, 1957-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 5)
    - E. Relationships of transport routes to land use, 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 6)
    - E-3 Industrial, 1955-1959; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 7)
    - E-4 commercial and industrial development created by highway, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 8)
    - E-5 Park and recreation, Circa 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 9)
    - E-6 Waterways, Circa 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 10)
    - E-7 Rural, Circa 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 11)
    - E-8 Relationship to each other, Circa 1955-1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 12)
    - F. Landscaping, 1954-1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 13)
    - G. Exclusive Pedestrian Accommodation, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 14)
    - H. Offbeat, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 15)
    - Bethlehem Steel, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22A, Folder 16)
    - Argentina - Buenos Aires, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 1)
    - Austria - Vienna, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 2)
    - Boston, Massachusetts [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 3)
    - Boston, Massachusetts [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 4)
    - Chicago, Illinois, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland, Ohio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 6)
    - England, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 7)
    - France, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 8)
    - Fort Worth, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 9)
    - Germany [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25A, Folder 10)
    - Germany [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 1)
    - Greece - Athens, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 2)
    - Hungary - Budapest, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 3)
    - Istanbul, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 4)
    - Italy, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 5)
    - Japan, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 6)
    - Lisbon, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles, California, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 8)
    - Montreal, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 9)
    - New York City, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 10)
    - Norway - Oslo, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 11)
    - Russia, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 13)
    - Seattle, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 14)
    - Spain, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 15)
    - United States - Misc., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 16)
    - Prints from Slides used in Public Speeches, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25B, Folder 17)
    - Stations: S's [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 1)
    - Stations: S's [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 2)
    - Stations: T - U, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 3)
    - Stations: V - W [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 4)
    - Stations: V - W [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 5)
    - Advertising, Promotion, Sales, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 6)
    - ADA Files, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28A, Folder 7)
    - Aerials, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28B, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28B, Folder 2)
    - Bike-In, Metro's First, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28B, Folder 3)
    - Automatic Fare Collection Equipment, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28C, Folder 1)
    - Awards, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28C, Folder 2)
    - Bladensburg: Dispatch, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 28C, Folder 3)
    - Bonds, Metro, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Bus Control Center, 1976 - 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Buses [1 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Buses [2 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Buses [3 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Bus Drivers [1 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Bus Drivers [2 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Bus Drivers [3 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Bus Garages [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Bus Garages [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Bus Garage: General, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Buses: General, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Buses, Historical, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Buses and Landmarks, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bus Mechanics [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Bus Mechanics [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Bus Mechanics 2 [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Bus Mechanics [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Bus Drivers [1 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32B, Folder 3)
    - Bus Drivers [2 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32B, Folder 4)
    - Bus Drivers [3 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32B, Folder 5)
    - Metro Logo [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32C, Folder 1)
    - Metro Logo [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32C, Folder 2)
    - Metro: Maps/ Seal, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32C, Folder 3)
    - Stations: General [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32C, Folder 4)
    - Stations: General [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32C, Folder 5)
    - IB0033 Construction Photos [Binder 1], June 1973 - February 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - IB0033 Construction Photos [Binder 2], February 1974 - December 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - File 1 - Prints, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 39B, Folder 5)
    - Photo Archives, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 39B, Folder 6)
    - Groundbreaking - MD, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Groundbreaking - VA, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Hearings, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Headquarters Building, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Independence Day, 1982-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Minorities, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - News, 1970's [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - News, 1970's [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - News, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - News, 1980's; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - News Stories, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Noise Prevention, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - OCCB, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Opening Ceremonies, 1970's - 1980's; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Opening Ceremonies, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Opening Ceremonies, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Other Transit Systems, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Penn Central RR Bridge, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Press and Political Train Rides, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Scenics, Landmarks, 1970's - 1980's; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Sec. of Transportation Rides, May 1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Sens. Bayh and Schweiker's Tour, April 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - NCTA - Staff and Office, 1960's; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Toronto, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Washington D.C. - Misc., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Washington D.C. - Traffic, 1962 - 1963; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - File 1: PLatform, Sub-station, Uniforms, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - File 2: Takoma to Van Ness, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - File 3: U-Street, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - File 4: Van Ness, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - File 5: Vienna to Wheaton, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - File 6: West Hyattsville to Zoological Park, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - ARCH: Clarendon to Crystal City, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - ARCH: Deanwood to Dunn Loring, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - File 3 [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - File 3 [2 of 2], Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Sample Photos, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Rails, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Staff, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Staff TPAs, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Station Designs, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Street Cars, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Test/ Evaluation Center, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Tokens/ Tickets, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Tours [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Tours [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Traffic, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Train/ Bus, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Train Control Center, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Trains: Exterior, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Trains: Interior [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Trains: Interior [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Trains: Operators, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Trains: Renderings, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - A-1 Ramps and Interchanges, July 1952 - August 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 1)
    - A-2 Tunnels, June 1957 - September 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 2)